digitalrev.com 2009-08-28

# Privacy Policy - DigitalRev.com

This is a privacy policy for [http://www.digitalrev.com](http://www.digitalrev.com/)

Contact Information

Our homepage on the Internet is located at [http://www.digitalrev.com  
](http://www.digitalrev.com/)

Privacy Policy Supervisor  
DigitalRev Limited, PO BOX No. 142  
Fo Tan Post Office  
Hong Kong

You may contact us by e-mail at [privacy@digitalrev.com](mailto:privacy@digitalrev.com) or by phone on (+44) 0870 141 7288

Opt-In/Opt-Out

Registering as a user and opening a user account is optional. To close an account, please visit our online support centre and submit a ticket. Your user account will be closed and all information removed from our server within 28 days.

To opt-out of our newsletter subscription, please follow the instructions found at the bottom of the newsletter. 

Dispute Resolution

If visitors or customers have any issues regarding the privacy practice of our website, please email [privacy@digitalrev.com](mailto:privacy@digitalrev.com) or write to our Privacy Policy Supervisor at the address above. Our Privacy Policy Supervisor will respond within 10 working days. 

Data Collection

When visiting websites, certain information about you and your computer may sometimes be collected. This section explains what information our Privacy Policy Supervisor will collect, and how it is used.

We may collect the following information about our visitors: 

|  | username data  
---|---  
| user's home-info data  
| dynamic.clickstream data  
| dynamic.http data  
| dynamic.interactionrecord data  
| dynamic.miscdata data  
| dynamic.cookies data  
  
We collect this information for the following reasons:  
| Completion and Support of Current Activity  
---|---  
| Website and System Administration  
| Research and Development  
| Affirmative Customisation  
| One-time Tailoring  
| Contacting Visitors for Marketing of Services or Products (Newsletter subscribers only)  
**  
User Account Registration Data:** The user account registration is optional. The data is stored on our server and is used for the sole purpose of speeding up your order process.   
**Data collected when customers place an order:** We collect customer's Physical Contact Address and Internet Contact Address, as well as credit card information (in the case of credit card payments) for the sole purpose of processing the order and delivering the goods ordered.   
**Newsletter Service:** Customers may opt-in and opt-out of our newsletter service. Our newsletter subscription service application may collect customer's demographic data in order to provide suitable content to subscribers. Customers may opt-out of the newsletter at anytime. Instructions on how to opt-out come with every newsletter sent.   
**DR Premier Service:** Our VIP programme is based on an opt-in/opt-out basis, and we collect customer historical purchase data for the purpose of marketing.   
**We do NOT sell collected data to 3rd parties:** All data collected is used strictly for the purposes defined in the above clauses. We will never sell collected data to any 3rd party individual or organisation.

Cookies

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not.

Our website uses cookies for the purpose of 'remembering' customers' choice of local site only.
